{
    "subject": "Eric_Byler",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Americanese",
    "human_readable": "Eric Byler directed Americanese.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8163166642189026,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Eric Byler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812821269035339,
            "question": "Who directed the film Americanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4043630361557007,
            "question": "Does Eric Byler have any other notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36300286650657654,
            "question": "Is Americanese a foreign film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34620729088783264,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Eric Byler's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3194410502910614,
            "question": "What year was Americanese released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24626684188842773,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in Americanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22687546908855438,
            "question": "Where can I watch Americanese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20473918318748474,
            "question": "What genre is Americanese likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20275525748729706,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Americanese?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Byler directed Americanese.",
            "html": "yago_13185_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Americanese likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_13185_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Americanese?",
            "html": "yago_13185_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might be explored in Americanese?",
            "html": "yago_13185_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13185_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n* The query is \"Eric Byler directed Americanese.\"\n* Let's evaluate whether the information in the documents supports this triple.\n\nThe documents mention:\n* Eric Byler as a film director who wrote and directed the feature film \"Americanese\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_13185/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt)\n* The same information is also mentioned in other documents, e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_13185/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Eric Byler is the director of the film \"Americanese,\" which was adapted from Shawn Wong's novel \"American Knees.\" Therefore, the triple \"Eric Byler directed Americanese\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}